Guide to the Thompson-Adloff collection on Southeast Asia, [ca.1960-1979]
Thompson-Adloff collection on Southeast Asia, [ca.1960-1979]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Thompson-Adloff collection on Southeast Asia, [ca.1960-1979]
4398
Virginia McLean Thompson, 1903-
38.2 cubic ft.
Newspaper clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Newspaper clippings on various subjects concerning countries in Southeast Asia.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Newspaper clippings on various subjects concerning countries in Southeast Asia.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Thompson, Virginia McLean, 1903-; Adloff, Richard.
Places:
Asia, Southeastern.; Philippines.; Indonesia.; Vietnam.; Laos.; Thailand.; Burma.; Cambodia.; Malaya.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Philippines. (Box 1)
- Indonesia. (Box 2)
- Indonesia, assorted subjects. (Box 3)
- South Vietnam. (Box 4)
- Vietnam, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 5)
- Vietnam, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
- Vietnam, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
- Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
- North Vietnam, Indochina Politics, Vietnam 1961, Bao Dai, Laos. (Box 9)
- Thailand, Foreign Relations, International Politics. (Box 10)
- Thailand, Press, Transportation. (Box 11)
- Thailand, Economics, Finance. (Box 12)
- Thailand, Foreign Trade, Health, Labor - Way. (Box 13)
- Thailand, Finance, Foreign Affairs. (Box 14)
- Thailand, International Political Parties. (Box 15)
- Thailand, Agriculture - Culture. (Box 16)
- Burma, Agriculture. (Box 17)
- Burma. (Box 18)
- Burma, International Politics. (Box 19)
- Burma, Social Cards, Pre-war Post-war Who's Who, Chronology, Communism, Miscellaneous 1960-1963. (Box 20)
- Burma, Foreign Relations, International Politics. (Box 21)
- Burma, Culture - Finance. (Box 22)
- Burma, Local Administration, Press. (Box 23)
- Burma, Local Administration, Labor and Population, International Politics, Religion, Press. (Box 24)
- Burma, International Politics. (Box 25)
- South East Asia, Chronology. (Box 26)
- South East Asia, Forestry - Political Developments. (Box 27)
- South East Asia, Agriculture - Education. (Box 28)
- South East Asia, 1968; Asia General, 1951-1952. (Box 29)
- Indochina, Agriculture - Foreign Relations. (Box 30)
- Indochina, Foreign Relations. (Box 31)
- Burma, Reports. (Box 32)
- Burma, Clippings. (Box 33)
- Burma, Clippings. (Box 34)
- Cambodia, Clippings. (Box 35)
- Vietnam, Clippings. (Box 36)
- Vietnam, Clippings. (Box 37)
- Indonesia, Reports. (Box 38)
- Indonesia, Reports. (Box 39)
- Indonesia, Clippings. (Box 40)
- Indonesia, Clippings. (Box 41)
- Laos, Clippings. (Box 42)
- Indochina, Reports. (Box 43)
- Malaya, Reports. (Box 44)
- Malaya, Reports. (Box 45)
- Thailand, Reports. (Box 46)
- Thailand, Clippings. (Box 47)
- Thailand, Clippings. (Box 48)
- South East Asia, Reports. (Box 49)